One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Beyond the heavy rain is a rainbow
hageshii ame no mukou kakaru niji wo mita
I'll know the easy answer's a lie
tayasui kotae wa uso dato shiru darou
Vow not to back down to the shouting
dekai koe nanka ni makenai to chikatte
I need you alone to understand tomorrow
anata hitori ni wakatte hoshii ashita
You gave me the time of my life
yume no youna jikan kureta anata
What do I look like? An ANGEL or a DEVIL...
watashi wa dou mieteruno? sorega tenshi ka akuma ka
Beyond the dawn, beyond the dawn
yoake no mukou yoake no mukou
There's so much I want to tell you
hanashitai koto takusan arun da
Filled with love, with love
ai kometa ai kometa
That can't be written down in a letter
tegami ni kakikirenai omoi da
A small hand in search of eternity
eien wo sagashita chiisana tenohira
"Kuma's Past -
Better Off Dead in This World"
An Elder, St. Saturn, has made landfall!
What?! When did he come ashore?!
And how?!
Everyone except vice admirals
and rear admirals,
move away from the town center!
You should refrain
from beholding his holy visage!
What's really going on?!
Even the admirals are at the beck and call of
just a single Celestial Dragon...
An Elder stands above all those gods!
Such a being...
...came all the way here
from Mary Geoise?!
I've only seen them in portraits!
What are those streaks of lightning?!
Bonney!
What have you done?!
St. Saturn!
How dare you, Jewelry Bonney...
You stabbed an Elder!
That man stands atop the very world itself!
Everyone! Aim your weapons!
This is no good.
Bonney! Get away from him!
Because of you...!
Silence, insects.
If I didn't want to get stabbed...
I would have avoided it!
Bonney-chan!
How dare you?!
How foolish...
Sanji!
It is no use.
What?! The blood vanished!
Seize Vegapunk and the others now!
Wait, you fools!
No need to rush.
They have nowhere to run!
Just ready your weapons!
Yes, sir!
Now...
This kind of sluggish work isn't like you.
Kizaru.
I apologize... I can offer no excuse...
Plus, I don't think...
...I'll be able to move for a while.
Let's see.
Strong Right!
I see... a pirate crew that cooperates.
Even a man on top of the world...
...wants our captain's head?!
Straw Hat Luffy.
Jewelry Bonney.
We failed to anticipate
your presence on the island.
But if your fate is strong enough to
escape this desperate situation...
I would love to see it.
And you, Vegapunk.
It is a pity that you betrayed us.
Thank you for your many contributions
to our military thus far.
Who should die first? Name them in order of who you will most grieve.
I want you to die with nothing but regret for
your rebellion against the World Government.
Why do humans always want to do
what is forbidden?
Wait! Stop!
This is strange!
Hey, can any of you move?!
No, I want to but I can't!
It's like I'm being held down!
What's going on?!
Even with my strength, I can't move!
If this isn't something scientific,
it must be a Devil Fruit power!
Oh no! Bonney!
You...
...killed my father!
Saturn!
Kuma...
He was born into a slave caste.
The descendant of a clan that once
committed a grave crime against the world.
The sole survivor of
the extinct Buccaneer People.
Bonney.
Ever since I was a child,
I wanted to be a hero who could save
the downtrodden and suffering.
"Justice"
Just like Nika, the Warrior of Liberation.
Everyone, get a good aim at her head!
Bonney-chan!
Leave her alone!
Don't shoot! She's still a child!
Then,
will he come and free me, too?!
Of course!
47 Years Ago, Sorbet
Kingdom, South Blue
He's a big boy!
Congratulations!
Oh, good boy.
Hi.
I'm happy to see you.
Thank you for being born, Kuma!
Um...
Doctor.
Is this about his blood?
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone.
Th-Thank you!
I'm back.
Oh! Welcome home.
All right. You're a good boy.
Up you go!
He's a cheerful boy!
Four Years
After Kuma's Birth
Thank you for waiting.
Kuma, let's clean up and eat!
Okay!
Someone gave us
freshly harvested potatoes today.
I'll help you clean and cook!
I'm sorry, Clapp! You need to run!
What do you mean, Doctor?
Run now!
The Government's minions
came to the hospital!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
You tried to help them escape.
You quack...
What do you people want?
I think you know.
You have to come with us.
You put up quite a fight.
Wait!
I'm the only one who has Buccaneer blood!
My wife doesn't!
Let her and my boy go!
Please!
All you need is me, right?!
Please...
Please let my family go!
Kuma...
Don't worry.
It's going to be all right...
Kuma... Live your life.
No matter how hard it gets.
Mom!
You must come this way.
We'll see each other again.
Stay strong, Kuma!
Dad!
Look! He's this young but this strong!
He's a Buccaneer slave-eh.
Hey! Hurry up-eh!
Yes, sir!
You irritate me-eh!
Why can't you move faster?!
That hurts! I'm sorry!
Stop crying! Or I'll kill you-eh!
H-Hey, Kuma...
What? Dad?
You're hurt.
Yeah, but it... it's nothing.
You've grown so much.
Are you doing okay?
Yes! My master is very kind and gentle...
So I'm very lucky.
Good...
Dad...
How is Mom doing?
Listen, Kuma...
Your mother...
Your mother's dead...
What?
She should be in heaven by now.
I think...
...she's better off that way.
Hey, Kuma.
You're strong.
Endure! Endure and survive!
Why? I think I'd be better off dead too...
The Warrior of Liberation will come!
He'll come to save you!
Who is that?
Nika, the Sun God!
TA-DAH
It's the name of a legendary warrior
that has been passed down...
...in our Buccaneer heritage
for generations!
One day, he'll come and take you out...
...under the sun, to the freedom of the sea!
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Nika is always laughing!
And he'll make people smile
with a rhythm like this.
What?
Shut up-eh!
You've waited a long time!
This is a triennial event
to test your skills!
The Native-Hunting...
38 Years Ago,
West Blue
...Competition!
This year, it takes place...
...on an island
unaffiliated with the World Government!
God Valley!
This island,
shamelessly named "God's Valley,"
possesses rich natural resources.
We'll hold a customary human hunt here,
and claim this island
for the World Government!
How dare you?!
Are you going to kill my people
for sport?!
You're insane!
This is our land!
Your Majesty!
What-eh? He is rude-eh!
Whoa-whoa!
Wait a minute!
St. Garling.
No head starts!
He's already taken down
the king of the natives!
Top contender St. Garling will have to
start with negative 10,000 points!
The handicap will make the competition
more interesting.
St. Figarland Garling,
a Holy Knight
So cool!
He lost a lot of points-eh.
But that felt good-eh!
As always,
in addition to the native rabbits,
we have a wide selection of...
...problematic slaves
and criminals to hunt!
I can't believe this!
He's a monster!
A slave escaped!
Wait...
Huh? Hey!
You guys were watching, weren't you?!
I-I'm so sorry!
Take responsibility and go get him!
There he is!
You fool!
You can't escape!
Stop messing around! Come with us!
No! I don't want to!
Shut up! Just come with us!
No! Let go of me!
Please! Let go of me!
No! I don't ever wanna go back there!
You little punk!
Crying won't do any good!
You shitty brat!
No! I can't take it anymore...
Stop resisting!
Go back!
- No!
- You little shit!
- Screw that place!
- Hey!
Why don't you kill me here?!
Even if I go back...
I will die anyway!
Shut up!
Sir!
They caught the escaped child.
It's the Buccaneer child.
Gee...
You can't just run away.
We're a team of ten,
all responsible for each other.
If you escape,
we'll all get killed!
Heehaw!
Hey! Hold it right there!
Are you the grand prize of this event?!
The Buccaneer boy?!
What?
You sure are big!
I heard you carry the blood of the Giants!
My big bro's big too, right?!
Only my face!
Cut it out, you fool!
Look at all those gloomy, miserable mugs!
Are you guys enjoying life?!
Shut up, you brat!
Oh, you guys...
Do you want to die?
Or do you want to live?
Isn't that obvious?!
But what can we do?
Work a miracle!
Emporio Ivankov,
a Slave
Ginny,
If you follow us, we've got a great plan.
I choose life!
How about you guys?!
I can't protect anyone again
mata daremo mamorenai no
It's my fault that the voice is fading away
kiekakaru koe wa boku no sei
I don't even have time to look down
utsumuku hima mo nai no
Gravel marks on my palms
tenohira ni tsuku jari no ato
Start moving again, my ship
mata ugokidase boku no fune yo
Though I can't fly in the broad sky
hiroi sora wa tobenai kedo
I can light up the deep sea
fukai umi wa teraseru kara
We
bokura wa
EVERYDAY owarenai
EVERYDAY, can't let this be the end
EVERYDAY makerenai
EVERYDAY, can't be defeated
We have something here to protect
mamoru mono ga koko niwa aru
This may not be what I expected
yosou chigai kamo?
But we can't stop now
tomarenai yo mou
We go on, sharing loneliness
kodoku wo ima wakeai susumu
Don't be afraid
ojikedukuna yo
I'm not the same person I was that day
ano hi no boku to chigau kara
No one can stand in my way
dare nimo jama dekinai yo
Now, move aside
saa doite
Conquer the world, believe in the future
sekai wo seishite mirai wo shinjite
Count up the nights
ikutsu mono yoru kazoete
What did you see? What did you learn?
nani wo mite nani wo shitte
To realize what was important
taisetsu na koto ni kiduita no